The eternal river that
never stops flowing.
It reminds me of cigarette smoke.
This kid's crazy if he thinks I'll
toss this much cigarette away.
Just hold your horses for
two minutes, would ya?
Help me!
Bummer.
Okay, relax, I'm coming!
You're safe now, kid.
You can thank me with a cigarette.
I'm whole thing.
Thank you.
I was just thinking,
wasn't there an urban legend that
beast folk meat was used in hamburgers?
Oh yeah, there was!
And there were fingers
with claws in it! So gross!
Can you not talk about disgusting
stuff while we're eating our food?
Uh, what is that? What's wrong? A finger?
Big sis?
Huh?
Hey!
Who the hell told her that it
was okay to smoke in the kitchen?
Yeah.
Man, thanks for helping me out
with all of this, Yannineko.
My porno manga and Yani
magazine deadlines overlapped.
I thought I was going to die.
Yeah, don't sweat it.
Mm-hmm.
Assistants these days aren't usually
okay with cigarettes, you know.
I draw my art by hand, so I need
my assistant in the room with me,
and they hate it when I smoke.
I gotta say, you're
pretty easy to talk to.
I'm naturally a shy person, but I feel
totally comfortable sitting here with you.
Not to sound rude, but I'm kind of
glad you got fired from your last job.
I'll make sure you're paid
well for all of this, too.
You okay?
Leave it to me!
Nice. Looks good.
You're doing great so far, Yanni Neko.
Oh
Wow, so this is your
little sister, huh? Hmm.
She's cute
Don't you think?
Yeah!
Promise you won't bring my
little sister into any of this?
I won't, as long as you
do what we agreed on.
Got it.
Great, because I just
bought this on Makari.
It's a high school girl uniform outfit.
Yay.
Truth is, I wasn't
really annoyed with you.
You said you wanted to make things right
after burning that artwork the other day.
I swear I didn't even care at all, though.
I was going to let it go.
But damn, you have a
great body, Yanni Neko.
You're gonna be the perfect
model for my next porno manga.
I love seeing an adult
woman wearing a high school
uniform instead of an
actual high school student.
This is so creepy.
Okay, let's go outside.
Why are we filming outside?
Well, this next story has
to do with outdoor sex.
So, I also need inspo for
the background material.
Okay, good.
Now stick your butt out a little more.
Ooh, wag your tail like
you're seducing me.
Perfect, just like that.
Alright, now try laying down.
Okay, now give me that
one-night stand look.
Hmm, I feel like that's not
erotic enough. Wait, I know.
Let's try tearing up your uniform a bit.
Holy shit, that's so sexy.
Now this.
Come on, just go with it. Here.
All you gotta do is act
like you want it real bad.
Okay, now let's try a different angle.
I want you to beg for it.
Don't stop!
You know just how I like you, don't you?
Yes, yes.
I've got so much good
material to work with here.
Cigarettes after work
always taste so good.
Now I want to go shoot in the
best location for outdoor sex.
A public restroom!
No outdoor sex in the park
is complete without a stop!
To the filthy public restrooms?
that have been completely
overrun by homeless people.
You ready?
Yeah.
I heard they're coming
out with a new burger.
Yeah, what kind?
Something with mushrooms, I think.
Just kidding!
Is that like some fucked
up Nancy you have?
That person wearing a schoolgirl
uniform, it can't be her, right?
We located the suspects.
We're detaining a suspicious
beast folk in her owner.
Over.
Imoko.
Wait, that was your big sister, right?
Can't be, because my sister's
hamburger meat. She's what?
Chainsmoker Cat.
Oh, this is pure gold.
Yanni Neko wasn't able to finish with me.
Imoko picked her up from
the police station and
had to forcibly drag her
to her parents' house.
I still had a few more pictures
I needed to take, though.
Oh, wow.
That outfit fits you perfectly, Kansai.
You kind of kept insistent,
so I finally gave in.
Seems to me you could
just be your own model.
Your body's incredible, Kansai.
Besides, this character is
supposed to be pure and innocent.
You're more suited for it than Yanni Neko.
Oh, you think so?
Hmm, yeah.
That'll do for now, I think.
It's over.
Stand straight for a second.
Yeah, sure.
I also need some reference photos
for the actual intercourse.
Act like you're a virgin who's nervous
about getting pounded into oblivion.
Don't let me down now.
Don't know if I can do this.
That's it.
Try another position. Like this.
It was a slutty little kitty cat!
Your strawberry milk.
Sorry to keep you...
The hell is wrong with you, you damn cat!
You spilled the boss's
strawberry milk all over him!
Little, you're gonna pay for
disrespecting the Kodan family! Hey!
Don't you dare lay a
finger on her, Katsurada!
Sorry, sir.
Katsurada, have you forgotten
what our boss here always says?
Uh, no, sir.
Don't pick fights with the civilians.
Yes, very good.
Forgive me, Mr. Kazushi.
It's quite all right.
We've known Yanni here since she was just
a runt, no bigger than a grain of rice.
Seeing her all grown up, I'm so proud
of her, it damn near makes me cry.
My bad, sir.
Oh hey boss I lost track
of the time we have that
newcomer award meeting
we Should get going boss
right just give me a second
Shibata uh sure the thing
is at This rate the rookies
who have any potential
All right, FINISHED!
Hey, Yanni!
Still busy with work or what?
You told me we would play Neon
Revo at some point, remember?
Hey, Hamaneco!
Yeah, I finished hey aren't we going
it'll be fine if we're a little late
So he's a small tits kind of guy
Shane smoke a cat
is there a booger hanging out
of my nose or something no
it's just that this is the first
time i've actually seen you
read so uh what exactly are
you reading anyway i found it
on kakeyome it's a story they
just posted kakeyome i love
that site i read stuff on it
all the time i don't remember
asking you well is it
interesting sure it's free so i'm
just reading it to kill time
but i am getting a little tired
of all these enemies to lovers
stories i know what you mean
i've read on tropes are
the worst right it's all
because of the ranking system
people want more readers
so they fall back on whatever
trope is already popular
to them it becomes less
about creating something
meaningful and more about
seeking validation they're
missing the whole point i
mean these aren't published
authors they should write
whatever they want that's
the whole There's no
point of doing it online,
isn't it?
Anyway, I was wondering, I...
No, a friend that I have
writes stories on Kakeyome.
I wanted to know if you could read
one and give me your honest opinion.
So you write stories on there?
Yeah, I mean my friend does.
The title of it is The
Melancholy of the Dragon Major.
It's kind of a dramatic fantasy story.
Oh, and by the way,
major is like the job title, because
in that world, every character...
Just shut up and let me read it.
Huh.
Hmm.
Well, I don't really get it.
Uh, you don't?
Yeah, neither did I.
My friend just started writing,
so that's most likely why.
They haven't had much practice.
Tell them to write an enemies
to lovers story, then.
Okay, I'll tell them.
Hey, you know what?
I should really be on my
way home now. See you.
Okay, I'll see you later.
Ah.
Chain-smoker cat
Is this Friday wait wrong place is this
the neon magazine office here from the
Hitosubashi family Sunday
group bring out your
editor-in-chief Kazushi
why are you so loud?
I'm the editor-in-chief, Kazushi.
What do you little punks want?
Asshole!
Our boss got a rude
email from you, Grandpa!
Give us a guest chapter,
unless you're scared.
No one disrespects our boss!
Lights out, motherfucker!
Oh, bastard.
Serves you right.
You should have been happy with
Kumita, but you just had to push it.
What the hell?
Why didn't he drop dead?
Copy of After Neon?
People joke they're so thick they could
be used as a weapon, but it's bulletproof?
Is Sheet the award booklets inside?
That only increased the thickness!
Oh, Land of the Lustrous II, that's born!
So the old bastard's an old pervert!
This is afternoon, I thought it said nyan.
Maybe I am getting old after all.
You boys done embarrassing yourselves yet?
Does stuff like this always happen here?
About once a year, I'd say.
Boss!
Call an ambulance! Boss!
It appears one stray bullet
went through his heart.
I'm afraid there's nothing we can do.
You should prepare yourselves.
Oh, damn it!
If only the afternoon beach manga project
had been approved before this happened!
Boss really cared about you.
He always thought of you as family.
He doesn't have long.
Will you hold his hand? Sure.
What's this?
He's breathing on his own.
This is incredible.
Oh, vitals are stabilizing,
his pulse is normal.
How is this happening? I'm high!
I'm a rock!
We're here for you.
He's helping, he can be in the sky!
Boss.
Chainsmoker cat!
First one here. Let's go.
Naked and ready.
Hey, guys!
My name is Hame!
Can everyone hear and see me okay?
You can let me know with your reactions.
Hi, Hame. Hi, Hame. Cute as
usual. Hi, Hame. We can see you.
I love you, Hame. Thank you!
Okay, that means we can get started.
For today's stream, I'm going to
introduce you to my neighbors.
All the girls in my building are super
pretty, so you're in for a treat.
Oh, look, I just found the first one. Huh?
Are you streaming?
This is Kansai, one of
the funniest girls I know.
Hey, I'm not even wearing
any makeup right now.
Come on, say something funny.
Now, hold on.
Don't you go put me on the spot.
Let me see, let me see.
Ah, time for the morning funnies.
What but because it's not morning
anymore it's afternoon okay
and that was Kansai let's find
the next person hang on you got it
all wrong I swear I'm funny You
can't just throw a gal in the deep
end and expect her to swim ask your
subscribers if they got it! Don't leave me!
Look, it's Hume.
No, no! Aro's an adult!
She just looks young!
Please don't report me!
Last one in drinks two bottles!
Hey, you're spilling all over me!
You've got it in my eyes!
I don't want to waste
it, so I'll drink it.
Hey girl, what's up?
Sorry to bother you.
Oh crap,
I can't show this!
Are you streaming me
without my permission?
Guess she's on and of her right now.
I'm scared of her.
This is just a hookah, it's not drugs.
Hang on guys, I said don't report me!
I was just joking about
the whole drug thing.
Do you guys seriously not
know what a hookah is?
I was set a warning for this!
Come on, everyone!
Nothing about this is even illegal!
You'll get my whole channel banned!
Get out, dumbass!
She kicked me out, guys.
Well, not to worry.
Let's move on to the next one.
Oh, hey, Hamei.
You came at the perfect time.
I'm looking for a model
for my new porno manga.
It's about a boy the main
character grew up with Who
actually turned out to be
a girl who's a ton of love.
I'm sorry, but I'm streaming right now.
Can you let go of me?
Or I'll do anything you want in return.
How are you as strong as a beast?
Never mind, next person!
Okay, now we have the
building's final boss.
Maybe she's not home.
Just as dirty as always, though.
You know there's mold everywhere.
You couldn't pay me to sleep there.
Quarantine the whole building.
I can smell it through my screen.
The door's open.
Maybe she is here?
Let's see if she's on the balcony.
Hmm.
Oh, there you are.
Hi, Yanni, what are you up to? Hi.
I'm eating bees.
Are you serious?
I wanted a new flavor in
my mouth other than smoke.
Uh, okay.
This is actually great content.
Anyone who's normal?
Oh, hang on!
I'm thinking about it, and there's one!
Okay, guys, this room belongs to the most
important person in the building, okay?
I don't think he'll come out
if I tell him I'm streaming.
What if I just secretly film him instead?
Is he naked?
What's going on? What is he doing?
Help! Help!
See you soon.
It's not so cold.
It's so cold.
It's cold. It's cold.
I don't want to be cold.
I'm going to be cold.
And I'm going to be cold.
I don't want to be cold.
The wind is going to come.
You